export default [
  {
    definition: "The text-align property specifies the horizontal alignment of text in an element.",
    question: "In this task, center the text horizontally using css.",
    answer: "text-align: center;",
  },
  {
    definition: "The CSS padding properties are used to generate space around an element's content, inside of any defined borders.",
    question:
      "In this task, add 50 pixels of padding to the top, right, bottom, and left of the red bordered box.",
    answer: "padding: 50px;",
  },
  {
    definition: "The margin property sets the margins for an element.",
    question: "Add 80 pixels of margin to the top of the red bordered box.",
    answer: "margin-top: 80px;",
  },
  {
    definition: "The text-decoration property specifies the decoration added to text",
    question: "Remove the text-decoration/underline from the <a> tag.",
    answer: "text-decoration: none;",
  },
  {
    question: "Remove the bullets from the list using list-style property.",
    answer: "list-style-type: none;",
  },
  {
    question: "Add a background color of #7F7FFF to the box.",
    answer: "background-color: #7F7FFF;",
  },
  {
    definition: "The color property specifies the color of text.",
    question: "Change the text color from black to red;",
    answer: "color: orange;",
  },
  {
    definition: "The font-size property sets the size of a font.",
    question: "Change the font-size to 25px.",
    answer: "font-size: 25px;",
  },
  {
    definition: "The CSS border properties allow you to specify the style, width, and color of an element's border.",
    question: "Add a border of 2px solid black around the box.",
    answer: "border: 2px solid black;",
  },
  {
    definition: "The border-radius property defines the radius of the element's corners.",
    question: "Change the black bordered box to a circle using border-radius.",
    answer: "border-radius: 50%;",
  },
];